Kael mss., 1939-2001 LMC 3004
Lilly Library
- II. Directors
  - Coppola, Francis Ford (Box 28)
    - Gardens of Stone., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 28)
    - The Godfather., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 28)
    - The Godfather: Part II., (see also: Box 113) (Box 28)
    - The Godfather: Part III., (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - One From the Heart., (2 folders) (Box 28)
    - The Outsiders., (3 folders) (Box 28)
    - Peggy Sue Got Married., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 28)
    - Rain People., notes, clippings (Box 28)
  - Coppola, Francis Ford (cont.) (Box 29)
    - Rumble Fish., (3 folders) (Box 29)
    - Tucker: The Man and His Dream., notes, press release, clippings (Box 29)
    - You're a Big Boy Now!, notes, clippings (Box 29)
    - Notes concerning Coppola (Box 29)
    - Interviews with Coppola., tear sheets, photocopies, etc. (Box 29)
    - Interviews by Kael with various people concerning Coppola (Box 29)
    - Clippings and printed items concerning Coppola, (see also: Box 113) (Box 29)
    - Clippings and printed items concerning Zoetrope Studios (Box 29)
  - Corbiau, Gérard (Box 29)
    - Le Maître de musique (The Music Teacher - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 29)
  - Corman, Roger (Box 29)
    - Bloody Mama., publicity, clippings (Box 29)
    - The Intruder., notes, clippings (Box 29)
    - The Trip., press release, clippings (Box 29)
    - The Wild Angels., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 29)
    - Clippings and printed items concerning other films (Box 29)
    - Clippings and printed items concerning Corman (Box 29)
  - Cosmatos, George P. (Box 29)
    - The Cassandra Crossing., (see: Box 121) (Box 29)
    - Cobra., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 29)
    - Rambo: First Blood, Part II., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 29)
  - Costa-Gravas (Box 29)
    - L'Aveu (The Confession - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 29)
    - The Betrayed., press kit, clippings (Box 29)
    - Conseil de famille (Family Business - U.S.)., notes, press release, clippings (Box 29)
    - État de siège (State of Siege - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 29)
    - Hanna K., press kit, clippings (Box 29)
    - Missing., (2 folders) (for publicity see: Box 113) (Box 29)
    - Music Box., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 29)
    - Section spéciale (Special Section - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 29)
    - Z., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 29)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Costa-Gravas (Box 29)
  - Costner, Kevin (Box 29)
    - Dances With Wolves., (2 folders) (Box 29)
  - Coward, Noel (Box 29)
    - Blithe Spirit., photographs (Box 29)
    - clippings concerning Coward (Box 29)
  - Cox, Alex (Box 29)
    - Repo Man., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 29)
    - Sid and Nancy., (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - Straight to Hell., clippings (Box 29)
    - Walker., (2 folders) (Box 29)
  - Crichton, Charles (Box 29)
    - The Lavender Hill Mob., photographs, clippings (Box 29)
    - The Titfield Thunderbolt., photographs, clippings (Box 29)
  - Crichton, Michael (Box 29)
    - Coma., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 29)
    - The First Great Train Robbery., notes, telephone message, publicity, clippings (Box 29)
    - Looker., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 29)
    - Physical Evidence., notes, clippings (Box 29)
    - Westworld., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 29)
    - clippings concerning other films and Crichton (Box 29)
  - Crombie, Donald (Box 30)
    - Caddie., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 30)
  - Cromwell, John (Box 30)
    - Algiers., photographs (Box 30)
    - Of Human Bondage., photographs (Box 30)
    - Son of Fury., notes (Box 30)
  - Cronenberg, David (Box 30)
    - Dead Ringers., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 30)
    - The Dead Zone., notes, review by David Chute, clippings (Box 30)
    - The Fly., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 30)
    - Scanners., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 30)
    - Videodrome., press kit, clippings (Box 30)
    - Materials concerning other films and Cronenberg (Box 30)
  - Crosland, Alan (Box 30)
    - The Jazz Singer., notes, photocopy of play, printed item, clippings (Box 30)
  - Crowe, Cameron (Box 30)
    - Say Anything., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 30)
  - Cukor, George (Box 30)
    - Adam's Rib., photographs (Box 30)
    - The Blue Bird., notes, clippings (Box 30)
    - Camille., photographs (Box 30)
    - Dinner at 8., (see: Box 121) (Box 30)
    - Gaslight., photographs (Box 30)
    - Holiday., photographs (Box 30)
    - Justine., notes, clippings (Box 30)
    - My Fair Lady., (see also: Box 113) (Box 30)
    - Rich and Famous., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 30)
    - Romeo and Juliet., study guide, photographs, clippings (Box 30)
    - A Star is Born., press release, photographs, clippings (Box 30)
    - Two-Faced Woman., photographs (Box 30)
    - The Women., (see also: Box 113) (Box 30)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Cukor, (see also: Box 113) (Box 30)
  - Curtiz, Michael (Box 30)
    - Casablanca., (2 folders) (Box 30)
    - Kid Galahad., photographs (Box 30)
    - Mildred Pierce., photographs (Box 30)
  - Czinner, Paul (Box 30)
    - Escape Me Never., publicity, photographs (Box 30)
    - The Rise of Catherine the Great., photographs (Box 30)
    - Stolen Life., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 30)
  - Dalva, Robert (Box 30)
    - The Black Stallion Return., Screening invitation, Statement from The American Humane Association, clippings (Box 30)
  - Damiano, Gerard (Box 30)
    - Deep Throat., (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - Daniel, Rod (Box 30)
    - K-9., clippings (Box 30)
    - Like Father Like Son., press kit, clippings (Box 30)
    - Teen Wolf., notes (Box 30)
  - Dante, Joe (Box 30)
    - The 'burbs.', notes, press kit, clippings (Box 30)
    - Explorers., notes, press release, clippings (Box 30)
    - Gremlins., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 30)
    - Gremlins 2: The New Batch., press kit, clippings (Box 30)
    - The Howling., notes, clippings (Box 30)
    - Innerspace., notes, press kit, photographs, color slides, clippings (Box 30)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 30)
  - Darnborough, Antony and Terence Fisher (Box 30)
    - So Loat the Fair., notes (Box 30)
  - Davidson, Martin (Box 30)
    - Eddie and the Cruisers., press kit, clippings (Box 30)
  - Davies, Terence (Box 30)
    - Distant Voices, Still Lives., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 30)
  - Davis, Andrew (Box 30)
    - The Package., press kit, clippings (Box 30)
  - Day, Robert and Basil Dearden (Box 30)
    - The Green Man., photographs, publicity, clippings (Box 30)
  - de Antonio, Emile (Box 30)
    - Millhouse., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 30)
    - In the Year of the Pig., publicity, clippings (Box 30)
    - Point of Order., notes, clippings (Box 30)
    - Rush to Judgment., notes (Box 30)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 30)
    - Materials concerning de Antonio (Box 30)
  - Dearden, Basil (Box 30)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 30)
  - De Broca, Philippe (Box 31)
    - L'Amant de cinq jours (The Five Day Lover - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 31)
    - Les Caprices de Marie (Give Her the Moon - U.S.)., notes (Box 31)
    - Les Jeux de l'amour (The Love Game - U.S.)., notes, printed item, clippings (Box 31)
    - Les Tribulations d'un chinois en Chine (Up to His Ears - U.S.)., notes, publicity (Box 31)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 31)
    - clippings concerning de Broca (Box 31)
  - Decoin, Henri (Box 31)
    - Les Inconnus dans la maison (Strangers in the House - U.S.)., publicity, photographs (Box 31)
    - Razzia sur la Chnouf (Razzia - U.S.)., publicity (Box 31)
  - De Gregorio, Eduardo (Box 31)
    - Sérail (Surreal Estate - U.S.)., press kit, clippings (Box 31)
  - Delannoy, Jean (Box 31)
    - Les Amitiés Particulières., (see: Box 113) (Box 31)
    - La Symphonie pastorale., photographs (Box 31)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 31)
  - Del Ruth, Roy (Box 31)
    - On the Avenue., photographs, clippings (Box 31)
  - Dembo, Richard (Box 31)
    - La diagonale du fou (Dangerous Moves - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 31)
  - Demme, Jonathan (Box 31)
    - Caged Heat., notes, clippings (Box 31)
    - Crazy Mama., notes (Box 31)
    - Fighting Mad., notes, clippings (Box 31)
    - Handle With Care., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - Last Embrace., publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - Married to the Mob., notes, clippings (Box 31)
    - Melvin and Howard., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - The Silence of the Lambs., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 31)
    - Something Wild., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - Stop Making Sense., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 31)
    - Swimming to Cambodia., notes, press release, publicity, printed item, clippings (Box 31)
    - Swing Shift., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 31)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 31)
    - Clippings concerning Demme (Box 31)
  - Demy, Jacques (Box 31)
    - Les Demoiselles de Rochefort (The Young Girls of Rochefort - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 31)
    - Model Shop., publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - Materials concerning other films and Demy, (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - De Palma, Brian (Box 31)
    - Blow Out., (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Body Double., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 31)
    - Bonfire of the Vanities., (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Carrie., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - Casualties of War., (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Dressed to Kill., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - The Fury., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - Greetings., press release, clippings (Box 31)
    - Hi, Mom!, notes, clippings (Box 31)
    - Home Movies., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - Obsession., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - Phantom of the Paradise., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - Scarface., (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Sisters., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 31)
    - The Untouchables., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 31)
    - Wiseguys., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 31)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 31)
    - Materials concerning De Palma (Box 31)
  - Deray, Jacques (Box 31)
    - Materials concerning various films, (see also: Box 113) (Box 31)
  - Deschanel, Caleb (Box 31)
    - Crusoe., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 31)
    - The Escape Artist., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 31)
  - De Seta, Vittorio (Box 32)
    - Banditi a Orgosolo (Bandits of Orgosolo - U.S.), notes, clippings (Box 32)
    - Un Uomo a metà (Almost a Man - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 32)
  - De Sica, Vittorio (Box 32)
    - Una Breve vacanza (A Brief Vacation - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 32)
    - Caccia alla volpe (After the Fox - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 32)
    - La Ciociara (Two Women - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 32)
    - Il Giardino dei Finzi-Contini (The Garden of the Finzi-Continis - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 32)
    - Ladri di biciclette (The Bicycle Thief - U.S.), (see also: Box 113) (for pressbook see: Box 121) (Box 32)
    - Miracolo a Milano (Miracle in Milan - U.S.)., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 32)
    - L'Oro di Napoli (The Gold of Naples - U.S.)., notes, publicity, photographs (Box 32)
    - Sciuscià (Shoe-Shine - U.S.)., (see also: Box 113) (Box 32)
    - Stazione termini (Terminal Station - U.S.)., (for clippings see: Box 113) (Box 32)
    - Umberto D., notes, programs, printed item, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 32)
    - Woman Times Seven., notes, publicity (Box 32)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 32)
    - Clippings concerning De Sica, (see also: Box 113) (Box 32)
    - Clippings concerning Cesare Zavattini (screenwriter/collaborator) (Box 32)
  - Deschamps, Bernard (Box 32)
    - Le Rosier de Madame Husson (The Virgin Man; He - U.S.), photographs, publicity, clippings (Box 32)
  - Deutch, Howard (Box 32)
    - The Great Outdoors., press kit, clippings (Box 32)
    - Pretty in Pink., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 32)
    - Some Kind of Wonderful., notes, clippings (Box 32)
  - Deville, Michel (Box 32)
    - La Lectrice (The Reader - U.S.), press release, publicity, clippings (Box 32)
    - Le Voyage en douce (Sentimental Journey - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 32)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 32)
  - DeVito, Danny (Box 32)
    - Throw Momma from the Train., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 32)
  - Diegues, Carlos (Box 32)
    - Xica da Silva., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 32)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 32)
  - Dieterle, William (Box 32)
    - The Hunchback of Notre Dame., photographs (Box 32)
    - Juarez., photographs (Box 32)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 32)
  - Dinner, Michael (Box 32)
    - Off Beat., press kit, clippings (Box 32)
    - Miss Lonelyhearts., press release, clippings (Box 32)
  - Dmytryk, Edward (Box 32)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 32)
  - Donaldson, Roger (Box 32)
    - The Bounty., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 32)
    - Cadillac Man., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 32)
    - Cocktail., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 32)
    - Marie., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 32)
    - No Way Out., clippings, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 32)
    - Sleeping Dogs., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 32)
    - Smash Palace., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 32)
  - Donen, Stanley (Box 32)
    - Arabesque., notes, clippings (Box 32)
    - Bedazzled., notes, publicity (Box 32)
    - Blame It on Rio., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 32)
    - Charade., notes, clippings (Box 32)
    - The Little Prince., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 32)
    - Lucky Lady., (see also: Box 121) (Box 32)
    - Movie Movie., (see also: Box 113) (Box 32)
    - Two for the Road., (for publicity see: Box 121) (Box 32)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Donen (Box 32)
  - Donen, Stanley and Gene Kelly (Box 32)
    - Singing in the Rain., photographs, clippings (Box 32)
  - Doniol-Valcroze, Jacques (Box 32)
    - Materials concerning various films, (see also: Box 113) (Box 32)
  - Donner, Clive (Box 32)
    - The Caretaker., notes, clippings (Box 32)
    - Luv., notes, clippings (Box 32)
    - What's New, Pussycat?, notes, clippings (Box 32)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 32)
  - Donner, Richard (Box 32)
    - The Goonies., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 32)
    - Inside Moves., clippings (Box 32)
    - Ladyhawke., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 32)
    - Lethal Weapon., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 32)
    - Lethal Weapon 2., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 32)
    - Scrooged., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 32)
    - Superman., (2 folders) (Box 32)
    - The Toy., press kit, clippings (Box 32)
  - Dornhelm, Robert (Box 33)
    - Cold Feet., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 33)
    - Echo Park., notes, clippings (Box 33)
  - Dörrie, Doris (Box 33)
    - Mánner (Men - U.S.), notes, clippings (Box 33)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Dörrie (Box 33)
  - Dovzhenko, Aleksandr (Box 33)
    - Clippings and printed items concerning various films and Dovzhenko (Box 33)
  - Downey, Robert, Sr. (Box 33)
    - Putney Swope., publicity, clippings (Box 33)
    - Up the Academy., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 33)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Downey (Box 33)
  - Dragoti, Stan (Box 33)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 33)
  - Dreyer, Carl Theodor (Box 33)
    - Gertrud., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 33)
    - Ordet (The Word - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 33)
    - La Passion de Jeanne d'Arc (The Passion of Joan of Arc - U.S.)., program, printed items, photographs, clippings (Box 33)
    - Vredens dag (Day of Wrath - U.S.)., (see also: Box 113) (Box 33)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 33)
    - Printed items concerning Dreyer (Box 33)
    - Clippings concerning Dreyer (Box 33)
  - Drury, David (Box 33)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 33)
  - Duffell, Peter (Box 33)
    - England Made Me., publicity, clippings (Box 33)
    - Experience Preferred...But not Essential., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 33)
    - Inside Out., clippings (Box 33)
  - Dugowson, Maurice (Box 33)
    - Au revoir à lundi (Bye, See You Monday - U.S.)., publicity, photographs (Box 33)
  - Duke, Daryl (Box 33)
    - Payday., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 33)
    - Materials concerning Duke (Box 33)
  - Duras, Marguerite (Box 33)
    - Le Camion (The Truck - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 33)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 33)
    - Materials concerning Duras (Box 33)
  - Duvall, Robert (Box 33)
    - Angelo My Love., press release, clippings (Box 33)
    - Clippings concerning Duvall (Box 33)
  - Duvivier, Julien (Box 33)
    - La Charrette fantôme (The Phantom Wagon - U.S.)., photographs (Box 33)
    - Poil de carotte (The Red Head - U.S.)., photographs (Box 33)
    - Pot-Bouille (Lovers of Paris - U.S.)., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 33)
    - Materials concerning other films and Duvivier, (see also: Box 113) (Box 33)
  - Dylan, Bob (Box 33)
    - Renaldo and Clara., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 33)
    - Clippings concerning Dylan (Box 33)
  - Eastwood, Clint (Box 33)
    - Bird., notes, press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 33)
    - Breezy., publicity, clippings (Box 33)
    - Bronco Billy., (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Firefox., (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - The Gauntlet., (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Honkytonk Man., press kit, clippings (Box 33)
    - Heartbreak Ridge., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 33)
    - The Outlaw Josey Wales., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 33)
    - Pale Rider., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 33)
    - Play Misty for Me., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 33)
    - Sudden Impact., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 33)
    - Materials concerning other films and Eastwood (Box 33)
  - Eberhardt, Thom (Box 33)
    - Without a Clue., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 33)
  - Edwards, Blake (Box 33)
    - Blind Date., press kit, clippings (Box 33)
    - Darling Lili., notes, clippings (Box 33)
    - Days of Wine and Roses., notes, clippings (Box 33)
    - The Great Race., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 33)
    - Gunn., notes, publicity (Box 33)
    - The Man Who Loved Women., notes, clippings (Box 33)
    - Micki & Maude., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 33)
  - Edwards, Blake (cont.) (Box 34)
    - The Pink Panther., notes, clippings (Box 34)
    - The Pink Panther Strikes Again., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 34)
    - S.O.B., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 34)
    - Skin Deep., publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 34)
    - Sunset., press kit, clippings (Box 34)
    - 10., notes, clippings (Box 34)
    - That's Life!, notes, press kit, clippings (Box 34)
    - Victor/Victoria., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 34)
    - Materials concerning other films and Edwards (Box 34)
  - Edzard, Christine (Box 34)
    - Little Dorrit., publicity, clippings (Box 34)
  - Eisenstein, Sergei M. (Box 34)
    - Aleksandr Nevskiy (Alexander Nevsky - U.S.)., notes, program, photographs, clippings (Box 34)
    - Bronenosets Poyromkin (The Battleship Potemkin - U.S.)., notes, printed items, photographs, clippings (Box 34)
    - Ivan Groznyy I (Ivan the Terrible, Part One - U.S.)., notes, publicity, program, clippings (Box 34)
    - Ivan Groznyy II: Boyarsky zagovor (Ivan the Terrible, Part Two - U.S.)., program, photographs, clippings (Box 34)
    - Materials concerning other films, (see also: Box 113) (Box 34)
    - Materials concerning Eisenstein (Box 34)
  - Emmer, Luciano (Box 34)
    - Leonardo de Vinci., publicity (Box 34)
    - La Regazza in ventrina (Woman in the Window - U.S.)., clippings (Box 34)
  - Enders, Robert (Box 34)
    - Stevie., clippings (Box 34)
  - Engel, Morris (Box 34)
    - Clippings concerning various films (Box 34)
  - Enyedi, Ildikó (Box 34)
    - Én XX. századom, Az (My 20th Century - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 34)
  - Eriksen, Gordon and John O'Brien (Box 34)
    - The Big Dis., press kit, clippings (Box 34)
  - Erman, John (Box 34)
    - Stella., (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Faraldo, Claude (Box 34)
    - Themroc., notes, press release, program, clippings (Box 34)
  - Fargo, James (Box 34)
    - The Enforcer., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 34)
    - Every Which Way But Loose., press kit, clippings (Box 34)
  - Farkas, Nicolas and Viktor Tourjansky (Box 34)
    - The Battle (Thunder in the East - U.S.)., publicity (Box 34)
  - Fassbinder, Rainer Werner (Box 34)
    - Despair., notes, clippings (Box 34)
    - Die Dritte Generation (The Third Generation - U.S.)., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 34)
    - Die Ehe der Maria Braun (The Marriage of Maria Braun - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 34)
    - Händler der vier Jahreszeiten (The Merchant of Four Seasons - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 34)
    - Lola., notes, clippings (Box 34)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 34)
    - Materials concerning Fassbinder (Box 34)
  - Feldman, Marty (Box 34)
    - Clippings concerning various films (Box 34)
  - Fellini, Federico (Box 34)
    - 8½., (see also: Box 114) (Box 34)
    - Amarcord., notes, clippings (Box 34)
    - Il Casanova di Federico Fellini (Fellini's Casanova - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 34)
    - La Città delle donne (City of Women - U.S.)., (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - I Clowns (The Clowns - U.S.)., clippings (Box 34)
    - La Dolce vita., (see also: Box 114) (Box 34)
    - E la nave va (And the Ship Sails On - U.S.)., clippings (Box 34)
    - Ginger e Fred (Ginger and Fred - U.S.)., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 34)
    - Giulietta degli spiriti (Juliet of the Spirits)., (see also: Box 114) (Box 34)
    - Le Notti di Cabiria (Nights of Cabiria)., notes, publicity, photographs, program, clippings (Box 34)
    - Prova d'orchestra (Orchestra Rehearsal)., clippings (Box 34)
    - Roma (Fellini's Roma - U.S.)., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 34)
    - Satyricon (Fellini Satyricon - U.S.)., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 34)
    - Lo Sceicco bianco (The White Sheik)., printed item, photographs, clippings (Box 34)
    - La Strada (The Road)., program, publicity, photographs (Box 34)
    - I Vitelloni., photographs, clippings (Box 34)
    - Materials concerning other films and Fellini (Box 34)
  - Féret, René (Box 34)
    - La communion solennelle., publicity, clippings (Box 34)
  - Ferrara, Abel (Box 35)
    - King of New York., press kit, clippings (Box 35)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 35)
  - Ferrer, Jose (Box 35)
    - The High Cost of Loving., photographs (Box 35)
    - The Great Man., photographs (Box 35)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 35)
    - Clippings concerning Ferrer (Box 35)
  - Ferreri, Marco (Box 35)
    - Storie di ordinaria follia (Tales of Ordinary Madness - U.S.)., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 35)
    - Materials concerning other films and Ferreri (Box 35)
  - Feuillade, Louis (Box 35)
    - Note and clippings concerning a film and Feuillade (Box 35)
  - Feyder, Jacques (Box 35)
    - La Kermesse héroïque (Carnival in Flanders - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 35)
  - Figgis, Mike (Box 35)
    - Internal Affairs., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 35)
    - Stormy Monday., notes, clippings (Box 35)
  - Finney, Albert (Box 35)
    - Charlie Bubbles., notes, clippings (Box 35)